export const AskedQuestionsAccordion = [
  {
    id: "1",
    question: "Do I need to book the Alcatraz Tour in advance?",
    answer:
      "Yeah, mostly. Tours often sell out days or even weeks ahead, especially during summer and holiday periods. We suggest you reserve tickets in advance so you don’t miss this amazing tour of Alcatraz.",
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    question: "How do I purchase a Ticket?",
    answer:
      "Simply choose your date & time and book directly from our website. Only card payments are allowed; no cash. And yes, the tickets should be in the name of the attendee. During the tour, the person whose name is present on the ticket should be there with a valid ID.",
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    question:
      "How do I book Alcatraz tickets as a tour operator or travel agent?",
    answer:
      "Even if you are a travel agent or operator, you still need to book the ticket in the client's name and credit card.",
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    question: "How often do ferries run and what are the departure times?",
    answer:
      "Ferries run every 30 to 40 minutes from morning to early evening. Schedules may vary slightly by season. The time duration for a day tour is, like, from 8:40 AM to 3:50 PM, and for Alcatraz night tour, time is Tuesdays-Saturdays (5:55pm, 6:30pm, and 7:05pm).",
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    question: "What if I miss my ferry?",
    answer:
      "If you miss your ferry to Alcatraz, you cannot have another one. Tickets are for a specific period of time. In case you miss it, you lose your tour to Alcatraz Island. Then you need to book a new ticket.",
  },
  {
    id: "6",
    question: "Can I reschedule or get a refund?",
    answer:
      "Reschedule and refund options are only available if you inform us minimum 72 hours before your departure time. Then you can have your refund. In any other case, a refund is not possible or allowed.",
  },
  {
    id: "7",
    question: "Are National Park Passes accepted?",
    answer: "No, National Park Passes are not acceptable.",
  },
  {
    id: "8",
    question: "Is food available on the island?",
    answer:
      "No, food is not available on the Island. You can buy food and drinks before arriving at the ferry. Eating on the Island is not permitted in some areas, but you can have a water bottle or snacks with you.",
  },
  {
    id: "9",
    question: "Which languages are supported for the audio tour?",
    answer:
      "An audio tour is available in 10 languages. These include English, Spanish, French, German, Italian, Japanese, Dutch, Mandarin, Portuguese, and Korean.",
  },
  {
    id: "10",
    question: "When does Alcatraz open and close during the year?",
    answer:
      "Alcatraz is open 12 months a year except for holidays (Thanksgiving, Christmas, and New Year’s Day). But opening hours may change as per the season.",
  },
  {
    id: "11",
    question: "Is Alcatraz accessible for people with mobility needs?",
    answer:
      "Yes, Alcatraz offers a tram service called SEAT for visitors with limited mobility. Paths and facilities are mostly wheelchair-friendly. We try all our best to open our gates to everyone.",
  },
  {
    id: "12",
    question: "Do I need an ID or the credit card used to book?",
    answer:
      "Yes. The primary ticket holder must bring a photo ID and the card used for purchase, especially when collecting tickets on-site.",
  },
  {
    id: "13",
    question: "Can tickets be cancelled or rescheduled?",
    answer:
      "Tickets are non-refundable, but some rescheduling options may be available depending on availability and how far in advance the request is made. May discuss with the customer service team.",
  },
  {
    id: "14",
    question: "Are toddlers free?",
    answer:
      "Kids under age 5 get in free of charge, but they still need a valid entry ticket.",
  },
  {
    id: "15",
    question: "Are minors allowed without an adult?",
    answer:
      "No, children under 18 must be accompanied by an adult guardian at all times during the Alcatraz Day trip.",
  },
];
